cheapestinindia.com 2013-06-05

# Privacy Policy

CheapestInIndia.com - Privacy Policy

Last Revised on: October 20, 2011

About CheapestInIndia.com

CheapestInIndia.com is a Shopping  / Deal / Product Search Engine .  Privately Owned and managed by CheapestInIndia.com Owners. Visitors are allowed search , View , Read And Rate (where ever Allowed) On the Price , Price Lists And Shopping Deals available on CheapestInIndia.com .

CheapestInIndia.com respects the privacy of its Visitors and is committed to protect their privacy in all respects. Should you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at admin [at] CheapestInIndia.com.

The present privacy policy governs the online information collection practices of CheapestInIndia.com ("we" or "us" or "CheapestInIndia.com"). Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather about you from your use of the CheapestInIndia.com website (the "Site"), and the ways in which we use and don't use this information. This privacy policy, including our children's privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means. To register for full access to the Site and in certain areas of the Site (for example, on contest entry pages), where personal information is requested, you may be asked for your age or birth date. You hereby agree that all information you provide to CheapestInIndia.com regarding age verification shall be truthful, accurate, and complete.

This privacy policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user and/ or member information collected on the Site. CheapestInIndia.com provides this privacy policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or discontinue using the Site.

Please note that any comment or other content posted on the Site becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information which is subject to this privacy notice.

Please read this privacy policy carefully. By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of the Site, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this privacy policy and our Terms of Use at the following link: Terms of Use .

What information is collected about our users ?

The information that we collect about you while you are using the Site falls into the following general categories:

1\. User provided information: We may collect and store information, personal or otherwise, that you voluntarily supply either while on the Site or in responding via email in connection with a feature provided on the Site. Some examples of this type of information include demographic information that you electronically submit when you sign up for access to certain features on the Site, information (such as your name or email address) that you electronically submit when you register for surveys or contests on the Site, information that you post on message boards on the Site, and information contained in search requests or questions that you submit to the Site. If you decline to supply or provide us with certain information while using the Site, you may not be able to use or participate in some or all of the features offered through the Site.

2\. Cookies information: When you visit the CheapestInIndia.com Site, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. CheapestInIndia.com uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the CheapestInIndia.com Site may not function properly.

In addition, third party advertisers or third party ad servers that place and present advertising on the Site also may collect information from you via cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies. These third party advertisers and ad servers may use the information they collect to help present their advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness, or for other uses. The use and collection of your information by these third party advertisers and ad servers is governed by the relevant third party's privacy policy and is not covered by our privacy policy. Indeed, the privacy policy of these third party advertisers and ad servers may be different from our privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.

3\. Log file information: When you use the CheapestInIndia.com Site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

4\. Clear / transparent GIFs information: When you use the CheapestInIndia.com Site, we may employ "Clear GIFs" (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users / members anonymously. In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

How is this information used?

1\. If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the CheapestInIndia.com Site, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the CheapestInIndia.com Site.

2\. We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may provide our advertisers with information about you and other visitors that will enable our advertisers to better target ads to specific types of visitors. We reserve the right to use and to disclose to third parties all of the information that we collect online about you and other visitors in any way and for any purpose, with one important exception viz. We will not use the information that we collect online from you while you are using the Site, nor will we authorize third parties to use such information, to mail or email promotional offers directly to you unless you have specifically informed us that you would like to receive promotional offers from us and/or from third parties. If you choose to receive these promotional offers, then your information may be used for direct mail or email marketing. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major CheapestInIndia.com Site changes or for customer service purposes).

3\. We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the CheapestInIndia.com Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user / member preferences and trends.

4\. We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the CheapestInIndia.com Site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, and contests.

5\. The Site includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third party products or services through the Site, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.

6\. We may also make some content, products and services available through our Site through cooperative relationships with third party providers, where the brands of our provider partner appear on the Site in connection with such content, products and/or services. We may share with our provider partner any information you provide, or that is collected, in the course of visiting any pages that are made available in cooperation with our provider partner. In some cases, the provider partner may collect information from you directly; in which cases the privacy policy of the provider partner may apply to the provider partner's use of your information. The privacy policy of our provider partners may differ from ours. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of one of our provider partners, you should contact the provider partner directly for more information. Be aware that we may occasionally release information about visitors / members when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our Terms of Service agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of the Site, the public, or the CheapestInIndia.com Site.

7\. Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that we sell some or all of our assets, or our Site is acquired by another company, information about our visitors may be among the transferred assets.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites, CheapestInIndia.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
CheapestInIndia.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on CheapestInIndia.com.

.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to CheapestInIndia.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......  
Google Adsense, Infolinks, Adbrite, Chitika, Bidvertiser, Valueclick Media etc

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on CheapestInIndia.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

CheapestInIndia.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. CheapestInIndia.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

When CheapestInIndia.com discloses information

* We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliate companies, or other businesses or people for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

* We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the CheapestInIndia.com Site.

* We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with any law or to respond to a court order or an order from any governing body or statutory authority.

* CheapestInIndia.com also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that CheapestInIndia.com believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of CheapestInIndia.com, our users / members or others.

Notification of change

We reserve the right at any time to: change the terms of this Agreement; change the Services, including eliminating or modifying any content on or feature of the Site; or change/charge any fees or charges for use of the Services.  
Any changes we make will be effective immediately on notice, which we may give either by posting the new Agreement on the Site or via electronic mail. Your use of the Services after such notice will be deemed acceptance of such changes. Be sure to review this Agreement periodically to ensure your familiarity with the most current version. You will always be able to tell when the version was last updated by checking the "Last Revised" date in the header of this agreement.  
Conflict resolution

We are committed to resolving disputes as soon as feasible and shall endeavor to resolve all disputes brought to our notice in keeping with the mechanism prescribed, within 15 working days of such receipt.

Contact Information:

If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

E-mail: admin@CheapestInIndia.com  
Website URL: http://CheapestInIndia.com
